1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8591 IS iPhone - Phone general tutorial.feature")
5. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/Login as a user with multiple sites/XCUIElementTypeOther - Menu (1)"), 30)
9. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeOther - Help"), 30)
13. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeOther - App Intro"), 30)
17. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeImage"), 30)
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - To start, add a new patient or select from your list"), "To start, add a new patient or select from your list")
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeOther - next"), 30)
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Add new or select an existing wound"), "Add new or select an existing wound.")
33. tap(findTestObject("IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeOther - Next (1)"), 30)
37. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeOther - Measure wound dimensions and color composition"), "Measure wound dimensions and color composition")
41. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeOther - Next (1)"), 30)
45. verifyElementText(findTestObject("IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Phone tuto/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Enter clinical information for documentation and reporting"), "Enter clinical information for documentation and reporting")