1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8570 IS iPhone - 10 Times failed login.feature")
5. delay(10, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
9. setText(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Sign In/XCUIElementTypeTextField - username"), "Test10times", 30)
13. setText(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Sign In/XCUIElementTypeSecureTextField - Passcode"), "123", 30)
17. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
21. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
29. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
33. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
37. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
41. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
45. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
49. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
53. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
57. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
61. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
65. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
69. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
73. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
77. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
81. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
85. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
89. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
93. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
97. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
101. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
105. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
109. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
113. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
117. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
121. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
125. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 30)
129. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Your account has been temporarily disabled due to repeated login failures. Please contact your administrator: samarir@masaratapp.com")
133. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)