1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8593 IS iPhone - Help.feature")
5. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/Login as a user with multiple sites/XCUIElementTypeOther - Menu (1)"), 30)
9. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeOther - Help"), 30)
13. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeOther - Help Center"), 30)
17. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Help"), 30)
21. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeButton - Cancel"), 30)
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeOther - Help"), 30)
29. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeOther - Send device info"), 30)
33. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Device hardware and software information will be sent to eKare for troubleshooting"), "Device hardware and software information will be sent to eKare for troubleshooting")
37. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeButton - Cancel (1)"), 30)
41. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeButton - Proceed"), 30)
45. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Information sent successfully"), "Information sent successfully")
49. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 30)
53. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/Login as a user with multiple sites/XCUIElementTypeOther - Menu (1)"), 30)
57. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeOther - Help"), 30)
61. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Menu and Other Sevices/Help/XCUIElementTypeOther - Send back up"), 30)