1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8258 IS Android - About.feature")
5. tap(findTestObject("Android/Patient Directory/Left Menu"), 30)
9. tap(findTestObject("Android/Patient Directory/Account Menu (left menu)/About"), 30)
13. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/About/android.widget.TextView - Katalon"), "Katalon")
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/About/android.widget.TextView - Katalon (1)"), "Katalon")
21. scrollToText("App version")
25. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/IS/Menu and other services/About/android.widget.TextView - IS 2.2.0"), "IS 2.2.0")
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/About/android.widget.TextView - Measurement Module"), "Measurement Module:")
33. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/About/android.widget.TextView - EK001"), "EK001")
37. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/About/android.widget.ImageView - Close x"), 30)
41. closeApplication()