1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8569 IS iPhone - Terms and condition Privacy and Policy.feature")
5. startApplication(LoginCreds.get("IPA"), true)
9. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Terms  Conditions"), 30)
13. tap(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Terms  Conditions"), 30)
17. delay(5)
21. tapAtPosition(44, 42)
25. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeImage"), 30)
29. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Privacy Policy"), 30)
33. tap(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Privacy Policy"), 30)
37. delay(5, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
41. tapAtPosition(44, 42)
45. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeImage"), 30)