1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8293 EU Android - Disable after 10 login attempts.feature")
5. setText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Username input"), "Test10times", 30)
9. setText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Password input"), "123", 30)
13. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
21. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
25. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
33. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
37. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
41. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
45. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
49. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
53. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
57. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
61. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
65. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
69. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
73. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
77. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
81. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
85. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
89. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
93. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
97. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
101. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
105. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
109. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
113. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Failed Login message"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
117. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Login failed OK"), 30)
121. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Sign in"), 30)
125. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Account Disabled"), "Your account has been temporarily disabled due to repeated login failures. Please contact your administrator: samarir@masaratapp.com")
129. tap(findTestObject("Android/Login Page/Account disabled OK"), 30)