1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8380 EU Android - Add Treatment.feature")
5. scrollToText("Patient ID: 24ui")
9. tap(findTestObject("Android/EU/Treatment Management/android.widget.TextView - Patient ID 24ui"), 30)
13. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.view.ViewGroup - Wound"), 30)
17. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.view.ViewGroup - Wound"), 30)
21. tap(findTestObject("Android/IS/Hard to find elements/android.view.ViewGroup - Treatment"), 30)
25. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.ImageView - Add Treatement"), 30)
29. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.ImageView - Add Treatement"), 30)
33. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - Next"), 30)
37. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - CLEANSING"), 30)
41. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - Acetic Acid"), 30)
45. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - OINTMENTS"), 30)
49. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - Zinc Oxide"), 30)
53. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - Save"), 30)
57. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - Acetic Acid (1)"), "Acetic Acid")
61. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Treatment and WCP/Add Treatment/android.widget.TextView - Zinc Oxide (1)"), "Zinc Oxide")
65. pressBack()
69. pressBack()
73. pressBack()