1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8783 IS iPhone - Delete Wound.feature")
5. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Patient Management/Search Patient/XCUIElementTypeTextField - Search by Name, MRN"), "91ui", 30)
9. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Patient Management/Search Patient/XCUIElementTypeOther - Current site"), "Current site")
13. delay(3, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
17. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Unlock Wound/XCUIElementTypeOther - Unlock, Wound 25072023 33M    MRN 90ui No Consent"), 30)
21. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Unlock Wound/XCUIElementTypeOther - Unlock, Wound 25072023 33M    MRN 90ui No Consent"), 30)
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Lock Wound/XCUIElementTypeOther - Wound"), 30)
29. tap(findTestObject("IOS/Wound Management/Unlock Wound/XCUIElementTypeOther - Menu"), 30)
33. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Delete Wound/XCUIElementTypeOther - Delete wound"), 0)
37. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Delete Wound/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Delete the selected wound All data, including all images and measurements, will be erased"), "Delete the selected wound? All data, including all images and measurements, will be erased.")
41. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Delete Wound/XCUIElementTypeButton - Cancel"), 0)
45. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Delete Wound/XCUIElementTypeButton - Confirm"), 0)
49. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Delete Wound/XCUIElementTypeButton - Confirm"), 0)
53. delay(2, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
57. tap(findTestObject("IOS/Wound Management/Lock Wound/XCUIElementTypeOther - Press Back 2 (1)"), 30)
61. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/Wound Management/Add Wound/XCUIElementTypeOther - x"), 30)