1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8569 IS iPhone - Terms and condition Privacy and Policy.feature")
5. startApplication(IPA, true)
9. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/Sign In/XCUIElementTypeButton - Allow"), 30)
13. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Terms  Conditions"), 30)
17. tap(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Terms  Conditions"), 30)
21. delay(5)
25. tapAtPosition(44, 42)
29. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeImage"), 30)
33. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Privacy Policy"), 30)
37. tap(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeOther - Privacy Policy"), 30)
41. delay(5, STOP_ON_FAILURE)
45. tapAtPosition(44, 42)
49. verifyElementExist(findTestObject("IOS/User Management/Terms and Conditions Privacy and Policy/XCUIElementTypeImage"), 30)