1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8570 IS iPhone - 10 Times failed login.feature")
5. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeTextField"), "Test10times", 0)
9. setText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeSecureTextField"), "123", 0)
13. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
17. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
21. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
29. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
33. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
37. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
41. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
45. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
49. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
53. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
57. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
61. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
65. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
69. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
73. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
77. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
81. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
85. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
89. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
93. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
97. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
101. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
105. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
109. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
113. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Login failed. Incorrect credentials !")
117. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)
121. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeOther - SIGN IN"), 0)
125. verifyElementText(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeStaticText - Login failed. Incorrect credentials"), "Your account has been temporarily disabled due to repeated login failures. Please contact your administrator: samarir@masaratapp.com")
129. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/IOS/User Management/10 times failed login/XCUIElementTypeButton - OK"), 0)