1. addDefaultPackages()
1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/EK-8259 IS Android - Switch between sites.feature")
5. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.ImageView - Menu"), 30)
9. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.TextView - Site"), 30)
13. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.TextView - Test1"), 30)
17. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.ImageView - Menu"), 30)
21. tap(findTestObject("Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.TextView - Site"), 30)
25. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.TextView - site user"), 30)
29. tap(findTestObject("Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.ImageView - Menu"), 30)
33. tap(findTestObject("Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.TextView - Site"), 30)
37. tap(findTestObject("Object Repository/Android/IS/Menu and other services/Switch between sites/android.widget.TextView - Katalon"), 30)